rivals.com 2000-12-02

# Rivals.com

 Fri. December 1, 2000  
|   
---  
  **•**  [Recruiting Experts](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=RECRUITING "Click here for 'Recruiting Experts'.")  
  **•**  [College Team Sites](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=RIVALSU "Click here for 'College Team Sites'.")  
  **•**  [High School Sites](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=RIVALSHIGH "Click here for 'High School Sites'.")  
  **•**  [MLB Sites](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=MLB "Click here for 'MLB Sites'.")  
  **•**  [NBA Sites](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=NBA "Click here for 'NBA Sites'.")  
  **•**  [NFL Sites](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=NFL "Click here for 'NFL Sites'.")  
  **•**  [NHL Sites](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=NHL "Click here for 'NHL Sites'.")  
  **•**  [Golf Sites](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=GOLF "Click here for 'Golf Sites'.")  
  **•**  [Motor Sports Sites](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=MOTORSPORTS "Click here for 'Motor Sports Sites'.")  
  **•**  [Outdoor Sites](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=OUTDOORS "Click here for 'Outdoor Sites'.")  
  **•**  [Soccer Sites](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=SOCCER "Click here for 'Soccer Sites'.")  
  **•**  [Specialty Sites](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=SPECIALTY "Click here for 'Specialty Sites'.")  
  **•**  [Fantasy Games](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=51&blip=FANTASY "Click here for 'Fantasy Games'.")  
  **•**  [Network Videos](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=10&NTL=1&L=1 "Click here for 'Network Videos'.")  
  **•**  [ ** _Story Index_**](http://rivals.com/default.asp?sid=0&p=2) ** __**  
  
|    

## Privacy Statement for Rivals.com

Rivals.com, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for all Rivals.com-affiliated Web sites. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. We will not provide or sell user-specific demographic information to any other person or business. We will only share this information on an aggregate basis. 

Our site uses cookies (user data collectors) to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes.

**_Advertising_**

Rivals.com works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>.

Advertisements served by DoubleClick appear on pages throughout this Web site. DoubleClick utilizes certain technologies to deliver specific advertisements to visitors to this site. Privacy issues surrounding this technology are disclosed in their privacy policy, which can be viewed at [www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy](http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy). 

**_Registration Form_**

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, gender or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the selected user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data for other purposes, such as tailoring the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers, but ONLY on an aggregate basis. We will NEVER share your address and personal data with any advertiser unless you specifically opt-in to one of our/their programs (a sweepstakes, for example). The choice to specifically identify yourself to an advertiser will always be yours. We will occasionally email you items of interest from some of our advertisers. You will have the opportunity to opt-out of such programs, and once again, your email name and personal information are never shared with those advertisers unless you choose to identify yourself to them by participating in offers that interest you. 

This site contains links to other sites. **Rivals.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**_Order Form_**

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, gender or income level). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared by Rivals.com with advertisers only on an aggregate basis. 

**_Contests_**

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, gender or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected from our users is used to bill the user for products and services. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared by Rivals.com with advertisers on an aggregate basis. Unless the user opts-out in the contest registration process, he has identified himself to advertisers and marketing partners and this information is not necessarily used in aggregate. 

We use an outside advertising company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. 

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

### Children's Guidelines

This site collects personally identifiable, online and offline contact information from all users interested in participating in contests, product offerings and other specific activities on this Web site. In some cases this information is more than is necessary to participate in the given activity. This site also gives all of its users the ability to read and to post in public forums. The site does not have a filter in place to exclude children from these activities without prior parental consent. Rivals.com uses its best efforts to make the content of its Web site acceptable for children's viewing.

 ** _Policies for Children Under 13_**

Safeguarding the personal information of children is extremely important to us. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the site. No information should be submitted to or posted at Rivals.com’s Web sites by children under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, Rivals.com does not collect or provide any personally identifying information of children under 13 years of age, regardless of its source, for any purpose whatsoever. Rivals.com may, however, collect certain personally identifying information to protect the integrity of the web site and the safety of children under 13 using the site. In the event Rivals.com collects such information, the information will be deleted from the Rivals.com systems each evening. No information collected from users under 13 years of age is used for any marketing or promotional purpose whatsoever, either inside or outside the Rivals.com Network. We do not allow children under 13 years of age to be listed in any member directories or to receive direct marketing communications from the Rivals.com Network or other third parties.

All users who register on the site receive e-mail confirming their registration. Users under 13 years old are notified that Rivals.com does not collect or store membership information without parental consent. Users under 13 years old have access to all of the content at Rivals.com, however without  parental consent, they are not able to post on Message Boards that require a membership, nor are they able to receive any communications from Rivals.com.

There are a number of emerging standards in the area of children's privacy that will affect how we process a child's personal information in the future. We are monitoring these changes and will redesign our systems in order to comply with these new requirements.

### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can, where applicable, make your preference known on the order form or registration form that applies to the activity 
  2. You can send email to [privacy@rivals.com](mailto:privacy@rivals.com)

### Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [privacy@rivals.com](mailto:privacy@rivals.com)

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

_413 Pine Street, Suite 500  
Seattle, WA 98101   
[info@rivals.com](mailto:info@rivals.com)_

|  |  |  |  |   
---  
  
   **Shop Now!** |   
---|---  
  
* * *

   **Marketplace**|   
---|---  
   **Specials**|   
---|---
